theeinfo.org 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Theeinfo.org

## Privacy Policy

Feel free to contact us, if any other information is needed about the privacy policy  
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which theeinfo.org collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of our website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by theeinfo.org.

## Web browser cookies 

www.theeinfo.org use cookies to provide the best experience of the website.   
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Non-personal identification information 

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to theeinfo.org and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Theeinfo.org has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
